const questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "WordPress allows website creation without coding skills.",
    answer: "True",
    options: ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the first step to launch a website?",
    answer: "Create an account on profreehost",
    options: [
      "Create an account on profreehost",
      "Install WordPress on your domain",
      "Choose a design for your website",
      "Add a new page to your site"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "To edit a page, use with Elementor.",
    answer: "edit",
    options: [
      "edit",
      "create",
      "delete",
      "design"]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> <i>A small business owner wants to create a website for free.</i><br><b>Identify the incorrect step in launching a website.</b>`,
    answer: "Purchase a premium hosting plan",
    options: [
      "Get a free domain",
      "Install WordPress",
      "Purchase a premium hosting plan",
      "Create an account on profreehost"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> <i>What is one correct way a user can edit their website's header or content?,</i><br><b>Which one of the following is a correct way to do this?</b>`,
    answer: "Use Elementor for content",
    options: [
      "Edit HTML code directly",
      "Use FTP to upload changes",
      "Use Elementor for content",
      "Reinstall the theme"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Profreehost provides paid hosting services for websites.",
    answer: "False",
    options: ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What tool helps design websites without coding?",
    answer: "WordPress",
    options: [
      "GoDaddy",
      "DNS settings",
      "Profreehost",
      "WordPress"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "To launch your website, first create an account on ____ .",
    answer: "profreehost",
    options: ["elementor", "profreehost", "godaddy", "wordpress"]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> <i>A user has installed WordPress and wants to start designing.</i><br><b>Identify the incorrect method to design a website</b>`,
    answer: "Code the website from scratch",
    options: [
      "Code the website from scratch",
      "Use Elementor",
      "Import a complete site design",
      "Install Astra theme"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> <i> A blogger wants to move their site to a .com domain.</i><br><b>Which one of the following is a correct step to do this?.</b>`,
    answer:"Update DNS settings in GoDaddy",
    options: [
      "Update DNS settings in GoDaddy",
      "Purchase a new hosting plan",
      "Delete old domain from WordPress",
      "Add domain to profreehost"
    ]
  }
];
